Is it accurate that the
rank and file no longer
supported Director Comey?
No, sir, that is not accurate.
I can tell you that
I hold Director Comey
in the absolute highest regard.
I have the highest respect
from his considerable abilities
and his integrity.
And it has been the
greatest privilege
and honor of my professional
life to work with him.
I can tell you also
that Director Comey
enjoyed broad support within the
FBI and still does to this day.
Yesterday a White
House press spokesman
said that this is
one of the smallest
things on the plate of the FBI.
Is that an accurate statement?
Is this a small investigation
in relation to all
the other work
that you're doing?
Sir, we consider it to
be a highly significant
investigation.